elitepronet.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy

EliteProNet's Privacy Policy

JANUARY 27, 2009 

This privacy policy applies to [www.elitepronet.com](http://www.elitepronet.com/), [www.elitepronet.info](http://www.elitepronet.info/), [www.elitepronet.com](http://www.elitepronet.com/), and [www.elitepronet.info](http://www.elitepronet.info/) .  This version of the Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above. By logging in to the system or using the website    
in any way, users consent to the Privacy Policy that is effective at that time. Even if users have read and approved a prior    
version, users agree to the version that is effective as of any date that they log in to the system or use the website. This website contains links from and to other websites that are not controlled by EliteProNet. EliteProNet is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to the EliteProNet.com and elitepronet.com websites. Please e-mail questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy to EliteProNet at support@elitepronet.com.  NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES MADE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY EliteProNet, Inc. reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.  **POLICY STATEMENT** **  
**   
elitepronet.com works with subcontractors, general contractors, homeowners and supplier. In order to make our    
website more useful to our users, we collect personal information in a variety of ways, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We    
have designed this Privacy Policy, and our underlying procedures, to best protect users' private information while making    
our website as useful and user friendly as possible. We endeavor to protect our users' private information to the greatest    
extent possible, but we cannot promise, and users should not expect, that personal information or private communications    
will always remain private. REGISTRATION OF SUBCONTRACTORS, GENERAL CONTRACTORS, HOMEOWNERS AND SUPPLIERS   
In order to submit a project request or enroll as a subcontractor, a user must register with our website, including creating a    
unique username and password. During the registration process, a user must provide contact information. We then use    
this information to contact the user about services on our website for which they have expressed an interest. By submitting    
a project request or enrolling as a subcontractor, a user expressly consents to being contacted by us by phone, email    
address or mail. INFORMATION COLLECTED WHEN SUBMITTING PROJECTS   
A project request includes the completion of a Submit Project Form and a Personal Profile Form. The Personal Profile Form    
is used to register the user to our website and is only required during the first instance of a project request. At the Submit    
Project Form we collect information that describes the scope of the project. We will also collect information relevant to the    
project such as contact name, address, bid due date, email address, and relevant information about the project. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM SUBCONTRACTORS   
Subcontractors enroll in our service online and complete a Registration Form and agree to a Service Agreement. During the    
registration we collect the following information: first and last name, company name, address, phone number, email    
address, membership affiliations, trades, billing address, username, password, credit card number, expiration date. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:   
The information collected is used to provide project information to qualified subcontractors within our network.   
Enhancement of Marketing Profile   
We may purchase third party marketing data and add it to our user database to target our advertising and provide pertinent    
offers to our users. We use this information to enhance the profile of individual users, and it is tied to users' personally    
identifiable information. This information is not collected directly from users, but from third party sources. User Profiles   
We use users' personally identifiable information to facilitate their use of our services. We create a personalized profile for    
each of our users by storing information we collect through a variety of mechanisms, which are explained below. This    
profile includes information on our users' viewing preferences, activities on our website and interactions with    
elitepronet.com. By analyzing our users' activities on our website and use of our services, we can improve our    
services and our website.  **DATA COLLECTION** **  
**   
Cookies:   
A cookie is a very small file stored on the user's hard drive that identifies the user to our website and assists us in data    
collection. We use both session cookies, which terminate when the user's browser is closed, and persistent cookies,    
which must be manually deleted.   
Session cookies allow our system to remember information about the user only during that internet browser session.   
Persistent cookies allow our system to remember our users, meaning that they will not be required to log in every time that    
they visit our website. Users may reject these cookies, or manually delete them. We do, however, offer several features only    
available through the use of a cookie; users who have rejected our cookies may not be able to access these features.  Log Files:   
We employ log files, which track certain information about your internet connection, including internet protocol addresses    
and internet service provider type. These log files are not linked to personally identifiable information of any user. By tracking    
this information, we are better able to analyze our users' needs and improve our services and website. **INFORMATION ELITEPRONET SHARES** Except as detailed in this Privacy Policy, EliteProNet does not share your information with third parties. The    
information we collect is to facilitate our users' use of our website and services.   
Aggregate Information: EliteProNet collects aggregate information on our users' use of our website, which we may share with third parties.    
This information does not contain personally identifiable information. Rather, this information is an anonymous summary of    
activities on our website. Legal Requirements:   
Though we strive to preserve users' privacy, we cannot ensure that users' private communications and other personal    
information will always remain confidential. For example, we may disclose personal information when required by law or    
when we believe parties are misusing or attempting to misuse our websites or services. Security:   
Users should also know that there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully access private communications and    
information. While we use several online and offline security tools, policies and procedures, we cannot guarantee security    
of the information we collect or that unauthorized access will not occur. Third Parties:   
Users of our website are always notified when their information is being collected for marketing purposes by any outside    
parties, except our affiliates or service professionals. Sale, Merger or Acquisition:   
In the event that EliteProNet goes through a merger, acquisition or asset sale, users' personal information will    
likely be part of the assets transferred. **COMMUNICATIONS FROM ELITEPRONET** Opt-Out   
Users may always "opt-out" of having their information used for most purposes. For example, users who no longer wish to    
receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving those communications by replying to the    
e-mail or e-mailing us at support@elitespronet.com.   
Notifications for Subcontractors Subcontractors in our network, or in our trial program, will receive regular communications from us regarding bid requests    
we have received, or directly from our users. We may use any contact information we have for our service professionals to    
provide such communications. Subcontractors may designate which method of communication they prefer on our website    
or by contacting Customer Service at support@elitepronet.com. Promotional Communications   
We send all new members an e-mail to verify usernames and passwords. Existing users will occasionally receive    
information on our services, products and special deals as well. We offer all users the opportunity to opt-out of these    
communications. Newsletter   
We may provide our users with a newsletter about our services. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for    
contact information such as name and e-mail address. We also offer users the opportunity to opt-out of these types of    
communications. Announcements   
We may occasionally need to send out service-related announcements. Users may not opt-out of these communications,    
though they may deactivate their account entirely. MANAGING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION   
Registered users can self-manage their personally identifiable information by means of logging into their secure and    
password-protected "Dashboards." Changes made are immediately reflected throughout our system.   
**  
****CONTACTING ELITEPRONET** Changes in Personal Information   
Users should e-mail Customer Support at support@elitepronet.com if their personal information changes or they    
no longer desire our services. Contact Information   
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at    
support@elitepronet.com.
